this is a time known as the great pirate era a countless array of pirates go to battle across
the seas in search of the one piece the legendary treasure left behind by gold roger king of the
pirates monkey d luffy a boy whose body turned to rubber after eating the gum gum fruit set sail to
become the next king of the pirates as luffy and his crew conquer numerous obstacles they capture
the unwanted attention of the world government which will use any means necessary to stop them
this site can't wait to see what kind of adventures up next with a charted course awash in danger and
intrigue the crew will cover path across the grand line to the new world
in search of a ship coding craftsman to help them reach fishman island the straw hat crew landed on
the sabaori archipelago this mission led them to rayleigh a craftsman and former vice captain of the
roger pirates the straw hat crew tried to lay low while rayleigh modified the sunny but they were
ambushed by a cyborg that bore suspicious resemblance to bartholomew kumar diablo shamba flambe shot
order 들어있 by claire
We need to get some rest.
I was up for a fight, but that guy was way too much for me.
I'm exhausted.
Overwhelmed and tired, they attempted to escape,
only to be ambushed by Centumaro of the Marines
and another pacifista.
I can't win. Let's run.
But not all together.
We need to split up.
They're splitting into groups.
Go after them, PX-1.
Now, come, come!
Come!
No, she got up, don't play, son!
Zoro!
Who? Who are you?
What are you? Whatever.
Just get the hell away from Zoro!
Oh, no, Zoro!
No! He got hit by one of those laser beams!
Kizaru?
When it seemed, things couldn't get any worse.
Navy Admiral Kizaru appeared,
thrusting the Straw Hats
into the most desperate situation they've ever faced.
Admiral Kizaru's fierce assault.
The Straw Hats face certain death.
Get ready.
Switzerland-
costs $5
Oslo?
Oslo?!
Oslo!
Oslo?
Oslo?!
I'll just stay down.
Hey, Warlord!
Let's go for another spin.
It's time you got your ass handed to you.
Warlord.
Shit.
Epil.
No one's ever stood up and walked away after that attack.
We just took down one of the seven warlords of the sea!
Yeah!
That's all it took to bring Kuma down? Seems a bit too easy.
What the hell? He's a machine! He's...
The damn thing's a cyborg!
He's a machine!
Funny, I don't remember asking for help.
If you could see past your own fat head, you'd realize how screwed you are.
What?
You think you could take down a real warlord that easy?
What do you mean by real?
We can discuss it later. We've got a few more guests.
Capture them!
A polar bear?
Oh...
Huh...
I had that, you know!
All right, Trafalgar.
You're going to explain now? If he isn't a warlord, what is he?
Great, what is it this time?
Zoro!
Crap! He shoots beams too? How are we supposed to beat these guys? At point blank like that, he's done for!
Zoro's in trouble! Come on, do something guys!
Usa!
Usa! Please!
Get away from him! Back up or else! Take this!
What? What the hell? Why? What is this? What's happening? I can't hit him!
I can't stab him! What the... What can we do?!
Usa! Please!
Get away from him! Back up or else! Take this!
What? What the hell? Why? What is this? What's happening? I can't hit him!
I can't stab him! What the? What can we do?
Trying? Damn it! Move your foot! I mean it! Leave him alone!
Step away from our friend!
You're wasting your time. I ate the Glint Glint fruit and now I'm made of light.
It's a Logia, you see.
He's made of light?
This is a nightmare. There's nothing we can do.
Zoro! Try to run away! Hurry!
I can't move. I'm too weak.
It's no use. The bastard's worn out. He can't save himself.
Now vent and blue!
Yes! Awesome work, Robin!
He just shifted in place!
Unbelievable!
It's cute how your friends want to save you, but you're far beyond help now.
Well then. Time to die.
You picked some time to come out of hiding.
Time to die.
You sure you want to do this, Dark King Rayleigh?
You picked some time to come out of hiding.
Don't go picking these buds before they sprout.
Their era is only just beginning, and I want to see what they do with it.
Rayleigh!
The geyser saved Zoro!
I was so scared!
So that guy is the Dark King? Interesting.
I'd heard rumors you were somewhere on the archipelago, but I chalked them up as ghost stories.
Yet here you are, sticking your neck out for these rookies.
You just can't shake those instincts, can you, Rayleigh?
Once a pirate, always a pirate.
I'd be more than happy to retire and feast and live out the quiet life.
But it's a little tough to do when the Navy keeps hanging wanted posters of me.
You were a member of the Roger Pirates, Rayleigh.
Do you really think your crimes can be forgotten?
But if we were to make an honest attempt at capturing you, that would require some serious preparation on our part.
Wow, I'm so relieved.
That old man has really got some power.
All of our attacks went through him as if he were a ghost.
But when Rayleigh attacked, it hit.
Why don't you just look the other way and let these kids go?
What's the harm?
Come on, what reality are you living in?
You know there's no way I can just let them off the hook.
Not when we have to answer to the Celestial Dragons.
Navy HQ's got to keep them happy and that won't do it.
I'd appreciate it if you don't interfere.
Hey, Usopp!
You guys!
Huh?
Grab Zorro and get out of there!
Let's go, Brooke!
Right.
Everyone, start running and look after yourselves!
We can't win this one!
We're too weak!
Get moving!
He knows when he's beat.
Well, ain't that a pain?
Frankie, come on!
Not before I let loose one final attack.
With all of my cola energy.
Go to fire!
Help that feel, you mechanical ass!
Now hurry, run!
Hey, old man, thanks a lot!
Sure thing.
Best of luck to you.
Sacred Yata Mirror.
I can't see!
I don't think he's trying to help us see.
You're staying put.
Feels good to hold a blade again.
Amano marakumo!
Soy!
This is disappointing.
I was expecting a laid-back, hassle-free island excursion.
Life is nothing but a series of surprises, Kizaru.
That light from before!
It's gone!
I guess the old man saved us again!
I was so scared!
It appears he's the Dark King, after all.
I've never seen anyone put Uncle through a fight like that.
We were so close to closing the book on Roronoa's days of crime.
PX-1!
Finish Roronoa off first!
He's barely alive!
Crap, this is bad!
Hey, Frankie!
Do me a favor and keep Nami safe, okay?
Just keep on running!
We'll be fine!
You take care of yourself, okay?
What are you doing, Sanji?
I've got to help Moose up and Zoro!
Put me down.
Huh?
Just leave me.
Save yourself.
Ah, don't be a moron!
Right now, you're even more weak and useless than I am!
We're getting out of here together!
Those were Luffy's orders and I'm sticking to him!
Huh?
Wait, do I hear...
Come on, hurry up, Moose up!
You go on without me!
It's fine, I'll hold him back!
No, don't do it, Brooke!
You don't know how strong he is!
He'll rip you apart!
Never fear!
Run on, my friend!
This is what must be done!
There comes a time when a man must put everything on the line!
No bones about it.
That was pretty pointless.
Brooke, no!
Go away!
Leave me alone!
Get the hell away from them, you stupid cyborg!
Oh, my leg!
Move, Sanji!
He's gonna shoot you!
Moron, why aren't you running?
Huh?
Even if you distract me, my subordinates are quite capable on their own.
I dropped you!
I'm sorry, Zoro!
It was an accident!
It's an accident!
Big jerk!
Who said I was done with you?
Damn it!
Stop and fight me!
Looks like they're in trouble over there!
You've got plenty of trouble yourself.
But just to be fair, I won't use my battle axe on you this time.
That took my show!
Luffy! Hi, how can his attacks work on him
when Luffy's made of rubber? What the hell?
Chopper, we have to keep moving.
Sachi!
Everybody's gonna die!
No, Chopper, it's too dangerous!
Get the hell away from my friends!
Now, rumble ball!
It's Chopper!
I like Little Chopper better!
What exactly am I looking at?
That's even worse than what the others told me.
That's an interesting power you've got there.
It's too bad you don't seem to have any control over it.
Luffy! Come on!
This is what it's come to? Even if he beats him, then what?
I don't know what's going on, but he seems confused.
Now's our chance!
Sanji!
Brook!
Get up!
Snap out of it!
Chopper bought us some time!
We gotta move!
You wanna live, right?
Hey!
You're blowing our chance!
Brook!
Sanji!
Stand down!
PX1!
Not another one!
This is officially too much.
I can't take it!
Just how many of these guys are there?
It isn't fair!
It's him!
It's the real Kuma!
What the hell happened here?
What happened here?
Nothing at all.
I see you survived, Rolo Noah.
Just barely.
I've got your mercy to thank for that.
What are you doing, Zoro?
This is no time to talk to the enemy!
Let's go!
If you could take a vacation, where is it you'd like to go?
Hey, Zoro!
Come on, let's get out of here while we can!
Where did...
Hey, Zoro!
Is he... gone?
Zoro!
Oh man, oh man, this is bad!
No.
What happened?
Where is he?
Zoro!
He just disappeared!
It's over.
They're all gone!
Brooke!
Reiki!
Robin!
Chopper!
Sanji!
Usopp!
Nami!
Zoro!
What's wrong with me?
I couldn't save a single one of my friends!
On the next One Piece!
Eliminated Friends!
The final day of the Straw Hat Crew!
Is that right?
Um, come on.
A little bit longer!
masking therail set in the link in the description box.
Felice!
What happened for his appointment?
Is that right to go?
At Solly this time.
He did...
Him.
If it's поехalta...
Of course!
You know...
Secondly...
Was about to go!
Jessica!
Seasonland...
Terry!
Jason...
Before we're here...
Has set?
He did it...
What's up?